happyuniverse.com 2019-04-30

# Privacy Policy

English | 简体中文 | 繁体中文

#### Released on November 11th, 2015

We, Happy Universe Studios Limited (“Happy Universe”), regards your information significant and release this Privacy Statement to inform you what information we collect and how we use it to personalize and continually improve you experience. 

This Privacy Statement applies to happyuniverse.com website, its services and the mobile applications of Happy Universe which collect data from you. 

#### Information We Collect

a. Personal Information. We do not collect Personal Information. “Personal Information” is information that identifies you or another person, such as your first name and last name, physical addresses, email addresses, telephone, fax, SSN, information stored within your device. 

b. Non-personal Information. We collect your non-personal information when you visit our website, including your device information, operation system, logs. For example, as many websites, we may use “cookies” to obtain the above information when your web browser accesses happyuniverse.com. 

c. Information you provide. We may collect your information when you communicate with us or you give us. 

#### How We Use Information

a. Personal Information. We do not store Personal Information and therefore we do not disclose your Personal Information. 

b. Non-Personal Information. We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your information. We do not combine Non-Personal Information with Personal Information (such as combining your name with your unique User Device number). 

c. Legal Reasons  
We will access, use or disclose your information with other organizations or entities for reasons that required by any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request; detect, prevent, or otherwise fraud, security or technical issues; protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Happy Universe, our users or the public as required or permitted by law. 

#### Security

Happy Universe is very concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your information. We do not collect Personal Information, and we employ administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect your Non-Personal Information from unauthorized access and use. Please be aware that no security measures that we take to protect your information is absolutely guaranteed to avoid unauthorized access or use of your Non-Personal Information which is impenetrable. 

#### Sensitive Information

We ask that you not send us, and you not disclose, any sensitive Personal Information (e.g., information related to racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religion or other beliefs, health, sexual orientation, criminal background or membership in past organizations, including trade union memberships) on or through an Application, the Services or the Site or otherwise to us. 

#### Children

We do not provide service focus on Children. If you are under 18, you may use our website when you are with a parent or guardian. 

#### Contact Us

If you have any questions or comments about this Policy or our privacy practices, or to report any violations of the Policy or abuse of the Services or the Site, please contact us at happyuniverseltd@happyuniverse.com. 

#### Changes

Our Privacy Policy may change which will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy from time to time, we will post any privacy policy changes on this page, so please review it periodically. If you do not agree to any modifications to this Policy, your could immediately stop all use of all the Services. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of any modifications to this Policy will constitute your acceptance of the revised Policy. Please note that none of our employees or agents has the authority to vary any of our Policies. 

#### 雅乐时空隐私政策

雅乐时空尊重并保护所有使用本雅乐时空网站、用户社区及移动互联网产品等雅乐时空提供的在线网络服务 (以下统称“雅乐时空网络服务”) 的个人的隐私。本雅乐时空网络服务隐私政策（以下称“隐私权政策”）规定：未事先得到您的同意，我们不会有意将涉及您个人隐私的内容透露给任何第三方，但本政策另有说明的除外。 

#### 一、雅乐时空网络服务和Cookie

在您首次访问雅乐时空网络服务后，雅乐时空会将一个“cookie”发送到您的计算机或移动设备，Cookie是一组数据，用于标识您的特定用户身份。雅乐时空使用cookie来提高我们的服务质量并更多地了解用户群体，雅乐时空会将用户的偏好存储在cookie中并跟踪了解用户搜索、浏览的趋势和模式，Cookie所记载您的个人信息均视为您个人隐私，雅乐时空将依照用户隐私策略进行保护。  
多数浏览器的初始设置都接受cookie，您可以将浏览器重新设置为拒绝所有的cookie，或在有cookie发来时进行提示。但是请注意，如果您拒绝接受cookie, 某些雅乐时空网络服务可能无法正常工作。 

#### 二、我们收集哪些信息

我们不收集有关您的任何特定信息，除非您特意提供了此类信息或者您已经同意我们收集此类信息。雅乐时空记录和保存的信息为您的匿名使用习惯数据和具备病毒、木马特征或其他可能会对您的计算机或移动设备造成损害的文件、超链接。除用户注册信息之外, 雅乐时空所记录和保存的信息包括: 时间、浏览器类型、浏览器语言和用户IP地址等。这些信息用于核实我们的记录并向用户提供更适合需要的服务。 

#### 三、雅乐时空隐私政策的具体内容

保护用户隐私是雅乐时空的一项基本政策,雅乐时空保证不对外公开或向第三方提供您的申请资料及您在使用网络服务时存储在雅乐时空的个人信息, 但下列情况除外：  
a）事先获得用户的明确授权；  
b）根据有关的法律法规要求；  
c）按照相关政府主管部门的要求；  
d）为维护社会公众的利益；  
e）为维护雅乐时空的合法权益。  
雅乐时空可能会与第三方合作向您提供相关的网络服务, 在此情况下,如该第三方同意承担与雅乐时空同等的保护用户隐私的责任, 则雅乐时空可将您的个人信息等提供给该第三方。 在不透露您隐私资料的前提下, 雅乐时空有权对整个用户数据库进行分析并对用户数据库进行商业上的利用 (包括但不限于公布、分析或以其它方式使用用户访问量、访问时段、用户偏好等用户数据信息)。 

#### 四、未成年人保护

如您是未成年人，您应在您监护人的同意下访问或使用雅乐时空网络服务。 

#### 五、联系我们

如您对本隐私政策有任何疑问或问题，请通过如下电子邮箱联系我们：happyuniverseltd@happyuniverse.com 

#### 六、对隐私权政策的认同和修订

您使用雅乐时空网络服务, 即表示您同意我们收集并使用您的资料 (如本政策所述), 并表示您认同本隐私政策。雅乐时空保留修改此隐私权政策的权利。如果您不同意雅乐时空修改的内容, 您可以随时取消获得的网络服务或停止使用雅乐时空的产品或服务。如果您在修改内容公告后15天内未主动取消服务, 则视为接受本政策的变更。修改内容公告后您如果仍继续使用雅乐时空提供的产品和服务亦构成对本政策变更的接受。 

#### 雅樂時空隱私政策

雅樂時空尊重並保護所有使用本雅樂時空網站、用戶社區及移動互聯網產品等雅樂時空提供的線上網路服務 (以下統稱“雅樂時空網路服務”) 的個人的隱私。本雅樂時空網路服務隱私政策（以下稱“隱私權政策”）規定：未事先得到您的同意，我們不會有意將涉及您個人隱私的內容透露給任何協力廠商，但本政策另有說明的除外。 

#### 一、雅樂時空網路服務和Cookie

在您首次訪問雅樂時空網路服務後，雅樂時空會將一個“cookie”發送到您的電腦或移動設備，Cookie是一組資料，用於標識您的特定使用者身份。雅樂時空使用cookie來提高我們的服務品質並更多地瞭解用戶群體，雅樂時空會將使用者的偏好存儲在cookie中並跟蹤瞭解用戶搜索、流覽的趨勢和模式，Cookie所記載您的個人資訊均視為您個人隱私，雅樂時空將依照用戶隱私權原則進行保護。  
多數流覽器的初始設置都接受cookie，您可以將流覽器重新設置為拒絕所有的cookie，或在有cookie發來時進行提示。但是請注意，如果您拒絕接受cookie, 某些雅樂時空網路服務可能無法正常工作。 

#### 二、我們收集哪些資訊

我們不收集有關您的任何特定資訊，除非您特意提供了此類資訊或者您已經同意我們收集此類資訊。雅樂時空記錄和保存的資訊為您的匿名使用習慣資料和具備病毒、木馬特徵或其他可能會對您的電腦或移動設備造成損害的檔、超連結。除使用者註冊資訊之外, 雅樂時空所記錄和保存的資訊包括: 時間、流覽器類型、流覽器語言和使用者IP位址等。這些資訊用於核實我們的記錄並向使用者提供更適合需要的服務。 

#### 三、雅樂時空隱私政策的具體內容

保護用戶隱私是雅樂時空的一項基本政策, 雅樂時空保證不對外公開或向協力廠商提供您的申請資料及您在使用網路服務時存儲在雅樂時空的個人資訊, 但下列情況除外：  
a）事先獲得用戶的明確授權；  
b）根據有關的法律法規要求；  
c）按照相關政府主管部門的要求；  
d）為維護社會公眾的利益；  
e）為維護雅樂時空的合法權益。  
雅樂時空可能會與協力廠商合作向您提供相關的網路服務, 在此情況下, 如該協力廠商同意承擔與雅樂時空同等的保護用戶隱私的責任, 則雅樂時空可將您的個人資訊等提供給該協力廠商。 在不透露您隱私資料的前提下, 雅樂時空有權對整個使用者資料庫進行分析並對使用者資料庫進行商業上的利用 (包括但不限於公佈、分析或以其它方式使用使用者訪問量、訪問時段、使用者偏好等使用者資料資訊)。 

#### 四、未成年人保護

如您是未成年人，您應在您監護人的同意下訪問或使用雅樂時空網路服務。 

#### 五、聯繫我們

如您對本隱私政策有任何疑問或問題，請通過如下電子郵箱聯繫我們：happyuniverseltd@happyuniverse.com 

#### 六、對隱私權政策的認同和修訂

您使用雅樂時空網路服務, 即表示您同意我們收集並使用您的資料 (如本政策所述), 並表示您認同本隱私政策。雅樂時空保留修改此隱私權政策的權利。如果您不同意雅樂時空修改的內容, 您可以隨時取消獲得的網路服務或停止使用雅樂時空的產品或服務。如果您在修改內容公告後15天內未主動取消服務, 則視為接受本政策的變更。修改內容公告後您如果仍繼續使用雅樂時空提供的產品和服務亦構成對本政策變更的接受。
